In today's video I'm going to talk about lollipops because I think it's a really unique item I want
to introduce you to. It's a new brand I'm going to show on my channel so stay tuned and learn more.
I got this box sent by Momspeak and it came from Portugal and inside are a few items.
I'm going to show you these first and now maybe you know why I said lollipops because obviously
it or not. But I think they look really colorful and yummy you put them inside your mouth.
So also I didn't want to disturb the YouTube algorithm. So the special thing about these
is that they're invisible gags and you simply put them inside your mouth and you can close
the mouth and you don't see it from your outside anymore. Well with this one and this one maybe
not with this one because obviously we have a bar here and you can already see
they come in three colors you can customize them with a leather belt
they're really squishy so I can bend them so really comfy to wear they're not
hard but really soft there are no sharp edges so you can't slice open the
instead of a mouth or something. The unique and innovative thing here is the
shape. You're going to put your tongue inside like in the middle in the inside
and then you can't move your tongue anymore and also it's going to fill out
your whole mouth so there's not a lot of room anymore or no room at all anymore.
With this one you have the shield part here as well which comes between your
teeth and your lips. You maybe notice from my dentist or from your bracelets such
stuff. They have a few different options here and they have a lot of different
sizes so you have to choose the size according to your jaw width so to say
and then you can find a perfect fit for you and you won't see it from the
outside. The leather straps are adjustable, two sizes adjustable and they
for different sizes you can also customize the metal hardware so silver or gold and this is
basically this one but with the bubble in front where the strap is attached to so this is obviously
going to be seen outside same as with this one so these are different varieties you can also have a
look at their homepage you can see all the varieties there and you can use my discount
code because then you get some percent off. And one last really special lollipop
they sent is this one. It's a double one and you can just use your imagination
for this. Anyway I hope you enjoyed this video. I hope I could show you something
new. Check out Månspeak and use my code and yeah I will see you in the next
video. Have a nice day. Bye!